const easyQuestions = {
	easyAdditionSet1: [
		{
			question: "1 + 1",
			answer: 2,
			choices: [3, 1, 4, 2],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "2 + 1",
			answer: 3,
			choices: [3, 1, 4, 0],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "1 + 6",
			answer: 7,
			choices: [4, 7, 3, 8],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "4 + 3",
			answer: 7,
			choices: [7, 5, 3, 6],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "3 + 3",
			answer: 6,
			choices: [5, 8, 6, 4],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "7 + 2",
			answer: 9,
			choices: [4, 9, 11, 10],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "5 + 5",
			answer: 10,
			choices: [9, 11, 8, 10],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "1 + 8",
			answer: 9,
			choices: [9, 12, 7, 10],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "4 + 8",
			answer: 12,
			choices: [12, 7, 10, 9],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "5 + 3",
			answer: 8,
			choices: [6, 10, 7, 8],
			question_value: 5
		}
	],
	easyAdditionSet2: [],
	easyAdditionSet3: [],
	easyAdditionSet4: [],
	easyAdditionSet5: [],
	easyAdditionSet6: [],
	easyAdditionSet7: [],
	easySubtractionSet1: [
		{
			question: "3 - 1",
			answer: 1,
			choices: [3, 2, 0, 1],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "5 - 2",
			answer: 3,
			choices: [2, 1, 3, 4],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "6 - 3",
			answer: 3,
			choices: [3, 2, 4, 1],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "10 - 4",
			answer: 6,
			choices: [4, 7, 8, 6],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "8 - 1",
			answer: 7,
			choices: [5, 4, 7, 8],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "12 - 3",
			answer: 9,
			choices: [9, 7, 8, 10],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "7 - 5",
			answer: 2,
			choices: [5, 2, 1, 3],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "6 - 6",
			answer: 0,
			choices: [3, 2, 0, 1],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "8 - 1",
			answer: 7,
			choices: [10, 6, 5, 7],
			question_value: 5
		},
		{
			question: "13 - 8",
			answer: 5,
			choices: [5, 8, 10, 6],
			question_value: 5
		}
	],
	easySubtractionSet2: [],
	easySubtractionSet3: [],
	easySubtractionSet4: [],
	easySubtractionSet5: [],
	easySubtractionSet6: [],
	easySubtractionSet7: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet1: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet2: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet3: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet4: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet5: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet6: [],
	easyMultiplicationSet7: [],
	easyDivisionSet1: [],
	easyDivisionSet2: [],
	easyDivisionSet3: [],
	easyDivisionSet4: [],
	easyDivisionSet5: [],
	easyDivisionSet6: [],
	easyDivisionSet7: []
};

export default easyQuestions;
